DIPENDRA NEUPANE

+977-9840071757 neupanedip3@gmail.com

Passionate software developer having around 8 years of working experience in different projects including taxation, automotive, e-commerce, etc, and comfortable working in different environments - independently, along with the team, and remotely. Seeking to leverage a strong technical role in full-stack software development and also ready for technical leadership as well in case of any opportunities.



Experience

Sr. Software Developer – 12/2021 to Present

Vesuvio Labs, Kathmandu Office

Working on an existing Automobils Claim-Management domain for adding new features, providing support and mentoring junior developers.

Skills Used: Asp. Net Core (C#), JQuery, MsSQL, Git

Full-Stack Software Developer - 10/2020 to 12/2021

AeriTech LLC, Kathmandu (Remote)

Being a Sr. team member of remote team operated from USA – worked a full-stack developer to add new features and create new projects mostly based on Automobils. Also get the chance to work on GitHub Actions for CI/CD setups.

Skills Used: Asp. Net Core (C#), ReactJs, MsSQL, Git

Sr. Software Developer - *05/2018 to 10/2020*

CloudyFox Technology, Kathmandu

Worked along with team and mentored junior developers - to create new features for sales incentive and loyalty programs related projects.

Skills Used: Asp.Net Core (C#), AngularJs, Angular, MsSql, Git

Software Developer - 03/2015 to 05/2018

Shangrila Microsystems, Kathmandu

Worked closely with Sr. software developers and designers. Being on my early days of software development career, these years has been really fruitful to understand the inside out of software development.

Skills Used: Asp.Net Framework (C#), ExtJs, PostgreSQL, Git

Skills Highlights

- Asp.Net Core (C#)
- ReactJs
- MsSQL
- Git
- Azure Cloud Computing

Education

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology (Distance Learning) -2016

Kuvempu University, India

Useful Links

LinkedIn, Github, Medium Blog

Hobbies

Hiking/Treking, Traveling, Football